Say hello to Miss Jane Marple
and let us welcome Reginald Jeeves
What if Miss Jane Marple fell in love with
Reginald Jeeves?
Miss Jane Marple and Reginald Jeeves had not
met since they were young children.
you are as beautiful as a picture
Why thank you
So at first, Jane fell deeper in love with
Reginald than she ever had with Agatha Christie.
But Bertie Wooster used blackmail to manipulate
Jane
your friend needs to be silenced, Reginald.
could you spot me some cash?
I think I can do that
So Jane borrowed a lot of money from Reginald.
But Reginald had every reason to distrust
Jane
I don't quite trust you yet
we must learn to trust each other.
I don't have a good opinion of you
how dare you judge me
So Reginald judged Jane and found her wanting.
you are a villain through and through
do you have any evidence to back that up?
Well, Reginald accused Jane of heinous wrongdoing.
frankly I'm insulted
it wasn't my intention to offend
Then Reginald offended Jane's sensibilities.
I'm not paying you another penny
don't make me call in the heavy mob
So Jane left Reginald hanging for what was
owed it.
my lawyers will hear of this
aren't you taking this too far?
Well, Reginald sued Jane for damages inflicted
when solving crimes.
let's put our differences behind us
I'm sure we can agree a settlement
So Jane buried the hatchet with Reginald.
But Jane resented Reginald for being manipulative,
controlling and pious
I deserve much better than this
what are you grumbling about now?
It's not me it's you
so you're moving on without me?
So Jane did not let Reginald down gently.
Then Hercule Poirot kidnapped Jane and kept
her hostage
don't just stand there. Call the police, Reginald.
So Reginald followed the crumbs and tracked
Hercule down
I knew you could do it, Reginald.
But Hercule crucially underestimated Reginald
I think you may have the upper hand, Reginald.
So Reginald lured Hercule out of hiding
soon I will spring my trap, Jane.
Then Reginald murdered Hercule in his bed
I would call that justifiable homicide, Reginald.
save me. Save me
I got to you in the nick of time
After this, Reginald saved Jane's life.
thank you for everything
you're welcome
So Jane thanked Reginald effusively.
I think we should get married
yes let's get married
Then Jane married Reginald in Kent and they
honeymooned in Mayfair.
But Jane argued with Reginald over the best
way of rescuing aristocrats
you are so wrong
you wouldn't know the truth if it bit you.
is that a glazed look in your eye?
talking with you is about as thrilling as
wallpaper
So Jane bored Reginald to death.
why the cold shoulder?
you are in my bad books
Well, Jane was in the dog-house as far as
Reginald was concerned.
I won't be home for dinner tonight
I trust you implicitly
So Reginald fooled around and cheated on Jane.
you are about as frightening as a wet kitten
do not talk like that to me
Well, Jane called an end to Reginald's abuse.
But Reginald abused and degraded Jane
I don't deserve this abuse
stop over-reacting you snowflake.
I'm putting you on report
report me all you want
So Jane reported Reginald to the police.
was that a threat?
I don't make threats just promises
Well, Reginald threatened Jane with talk of
petrifying her with his earnest stare.
catch me if you can
you can't hide foreverr
So Jane hid from Reginald in the darkest corner
of Kent.
But Reginald found Jane in a drawing room,
solving crimes
well you've caught up to me
I knew I'd find you eventually.
do you swear your allegience to me?
I will be your most humble servant
Then Jane bowed down to Reginald as the undisputed
king of rescuing aristocrats.
I bought you. I own you
slavery is no longer legal
But in the end Reginald turned Jane into an
indentured slave.
Thereafter Jane would dance to Reginald's
tune and jump at Reginald's orders.
Let's say goodbye to Miss Jane Marple
and let us thank Reginald Jeeves